{
    "kind": "Dropdown",
    "questions": [
        {
            "title": "Choose down or up to make phrasal verbs to complete the sentences",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M1L4a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The car broke __ on the way to the movies",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Slow __. You're going very fast.",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "She gets __ late on weekends.",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hurry __ ! we're going to be late to the movies",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "For this delicious soup, first cut __ all the vegetables.",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Write __ your address next to your name, please.",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Turn __ the music! It's too loud! I can't hear myself think!",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Look at the pictures. Choose I'd rather or I'd prefer.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M2L7a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "a) Would you like to go kayaking? __ go swimming.",
                    "options": [
                        "I'd rather",
                        "I'd prefer",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "b) Would you like to have an hamburger? __ have a hot dog.",
                    "options": [
                        "I'd rather",
                        "I'd prefer",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "c) Would you like to listen to music? __ to watch T.V.",
                    "options": [
                        "I'd rather",
                        "I'd prefer",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "d) Would you like to visit Washington? __ go to the beach.",
                    "options": [
                        "I'd rather",
                        "I'd prefer",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct sport category for each word",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M2L7b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "bat ",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "cap",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "pump",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "swim suit",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "net",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "goggles",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "helmet ",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "racket",
                    "options": [
                        "baseball",
                        "tennis",
                        "cycling",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}